[
    {
    "question": "What Gryffindor and their brother sneak back into the castle to help fight in the final battle?",
    "choice1": "Piers Polkiss",
    "choice2": "Colin Creevey",
    "choice3": "Peter Pettigrew",
    "choice4": "Leta Lastrange",
    "answer": 2
    },
    {
    "question": "Which house ghost met their end after people grew suspicious of their ability to cure the pox?",
    "choice1": "The Bloody Baron",
    "choice2": "Nearly-Headless Nick",
    "choice3": "The Fat Friar",
    "choice4": "Moaning Myrtle",
    "answer": 3
    },
    {
    "question": "The Gray Lady was the daughter of which Hogwarts founder?",
    "choice1": "Helga Hufflepuff",
    "choice2": "Godric Gryffindor",
    "choice3": "Salazar Slytherin",
    "choice4": "Rowena Ravenclaw",
    "answer": 4
    },
    {
    "question": "Along with Harry who was attacked by the dementors?",
    "choice1": "Dudley Dursley",
    "choice2": "Stan Shunpike",
    "choice3": "Padma Patil",
    "choice4": "Cho Chang",
    "answer": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Which Slytherin wanted to turn Harry over to Voldemort?",
    "choice1": "Gellert Grindelwald",
    "choice2": "Piers Polkiss",
    "choice3": "Pansy Parkinson",
    "choice4": "Gregory Goyle",
    "answer": 3
    },
    {
    "question": "What quidditch team does Cho Chang support?",
    "choice1": "Holyhead Harpies",
    "choice2": "Chudley Cannons",
    "choice3": "Kenmare Kestrels",
    "choice4": "Tutshill Tornados",
    "answer": 4
    },
    {
    "question": "Who was really themselves when Harry first met them?",
    "choice1": "Cho Chang",
    "choice2": "Bathilda Bagshot",
    "choice3": "Stan Shunpike",
    "choice4": "Parvati Patil",
    "answer": 2
    },
    {
    "question": "Which was the onyl staff member not to fight in the battle of Hogwarts?",
    "choice1": "Filius Flitwick",
    "choice2": "Minerva McGonagall",
    "choice3": "Poppy Pomfrey",
    "choice4": "Severus Snape",
    "answer": 4
    },
    {
    "question": "Who spoke at Dobby's funeral?",
    "choice1": "Luna Lovegood",
    "choice2": "Cho Chang",
    "choice3": "Padma Patil",
    "choice4": "Colin Creevey",
    "answer": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "Which Hogwarts founder's descendant founded the American wizarding school, Ilvermorny? ",
    "choice1": "Helga Hufflepuff",
    "choice2": "Godric Gryffindor",
    "choice3": "Salazar Slytherin",
    "choice4": "Rowena Ravenclaw",
    "answer": 3
    }
  ]